我们之前说到使用Sunshine指令去开启活动然后
We've talked about using intents within Sunshine to start activities and send
在应用间发送数据  但如果你要群发信息给
data between apps. But what if you want to broadcast a message to
多个应用呢  举个例子  系统要广播一个消息  说
many apps? For example, the system will broadcast a message, saying that the
设备正在充电或者即将重启  我们的方法是
device is charging or that it's just finished rebooting. To do that ourselves,
使用sendbroadcast的方法来广播一个指令  然后这些广播
we use the SendBroadcast method to broadcast an intent. And those broadcasts
就会被广播接收者接受  通常
are received by broadcast receivers, typically
就会简明指向接受者  使用指令
referred to as simply, receivers. Using intent
过滤器  就像之前一样  它们会表明那些广播是自己
filters, like the ones we saw earlier, they indicate which broadcast they're
感兴趣的  所以如果我们反馈的是之前的封装的暗喻
interested in. So if we return to our envelope metaphor from earlier, in
在是广播指令的情况下  你的
the case of a broadcast intent, your
封装会被写地址传递给任一
envelope is basically addressed to any broadcast receiver
感兴趣知道会此事件的广播接收者
that's interested in knowing that this event has
而它正是通过指令过滤器来实现的
happened. And it does that using intent filter.
所以广播指令正是通过每一个
So intents, which are broadcast, are transmitted to every
含有广播接受装置中的指令
app with a broadcast receiver that has an intent
过滤器的广播接收作用来告诉系统你的想法  这真的让我觉得很有趣
filter telling the system your ideas are intriguing to
然后我希望能分发给终端使用者
me and I wish to subscribe to end user.